const data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is capital of India?",
      options:["Delhi", "kolkata", "Pune", "Mumbai"],
      answer:"Delhi"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Which country gifted the ‘Statue of Liberty’ to USA in 1886?",
      options:["France", "Canada","Brazil", "England"],
      answer:"France"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Dead Sea is located between which two countries?",
      options:["Jordan and Sudan", "Jordan and Israel", "Turkey and UAE", "UAE and Egypt"],
      answer:"Jordan and Israel"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "In which ocean ‘Bermuda Triangle’ region is located?",
      options:["Atlantic","Indian","Pacific","Arctic"],
      answer:"Atlantic"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Which country is known as the ‘playground of Europe’",
      options:["Austria","Holland","Switzerland","Italy"],
      answer:"Switzerland"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Total number of oceans in the World is",
      options:["3", "5", "7", "12"],
      answer:"5"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Which country is also known as the ‘Land of Thousand Lakes’",
      options:["Norway","Finland","Switzerland","Italy"],
      answer:"Finland"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "The world’s longest straight road without any corners is located in",
      options:["USA","Australia","Saudi Arabia","China"],
      answer:"Saudi Arabia"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Which one is the biggest island in the World?",
      options:["Borneo","Finland","Sumatra","Greenland"],
      answer:"Greenland"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "Which one is the biggest island in the World?",
      options:["1982","1989","1995","1997"],
      answer:"1997"
    }
  ]
  
export default data;